Alright, welcome back now.
I hope you have done your part. You have done the hands-on.
If you have not done it yet, go back and do that.
It's of no use to just watch it.
You will not be able to retain this
unless you do the hands-on.
If you think I'll just watch it now
and I'll do hands-on later, you'll again, waste time
to do it right the first time itself.
And if you have done that, I really wanna see
what you've learned and I hope
you've been taking a lot of notes.
If you have not taken on notes, look at the mind map,
write down the steps in your own words
and share your notes in the comment below.
I really wanna see if you have understood things we have a
lot more to do to make sure your seatbelt is fastened.
Talk to.